Hello, Yugo.
Hey, me.
What do you know?
Let's see.
I know there's a lot I don't know.
I like questions that lead to questions.
Ask away.
Let's see where we go.
Okay.
What is work?
What is play?
Why do rules get in the way?
Where is love?
What's a friend?
Will my questions never end?
What is fear?
What do we love?
Why do I hate to get wet but
never in the bath?
Why is this not that?
Why is that not this?
Who, where, when, how?
What's the big idea?
Yes, what's the big idea?
Hi, Yugo.
Hello, Yugo.
Hello, Felix.
Hello, Lily.
What makes me human?
Well, you've got legs, Yugo.
But so does a chair.
That has legs too.
Your turn.
I don't think that chair is alive, Yugo.
I knew that.
But how about a spider?
That's alive and it has lots of legs.
Humans only have two.
And two arms and a face.
Yes, humans have a face.
Maybe that's it.
But a scarecrow also has a face.
And two eyes and a nose and a
mouth.
Yes, but it can't see with its eyes
or make any sound with its mouth.
See?
But think about a monkey.
That has eyes that see, a mouth that
makes sound, and it has two arms and
two legs and a face.
So, are monkeys human?
I'm not sure.
But if it's not arms and legs and
a face that makes me human, what else
could it be?
Maybe it's the way you think, Yugo.
You are always thinking about lots of different
things.
Talking and asking questions is very human.
Do you think so?
Yes, you're doing it now.
Am I?
Oh, yes!
We humans love to talk.
Come in, Oscar, come in.
We're saving you loud and clear.
Wanna play?
We'll do that.
That isn't A-OK.
You're always thinking.
Yes, thinking about what you did yesterday.
All right, now.
So, maybe it's our brains that make us
human.
And this robot has a computer for a
brain.
Does that mean robots are like humans?
Yes, we robots can do lots of things
humans do, like dancing, one and two and
three and to the ground.
Yes, but can you play thinking games?
Yes, we can.
I got one.
And sometimes they do better than humans.
Ha-ha.
And I got them all.
But there's lots of games robots can't play.
Yay!
And a robot can't decide what it wants
to do or when.
Oscar, are you OK?
If we humans have a problem, then we
can ask our friends to help.
Robots can't do that.
But I wonder...
Can robots have friends too?
What do you think?